<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<LanguageData>
    <!-- Groups -->
    <TKUtils.PawnCommands>Pawn Commands</TKUtils.PawnCommands>
    
    <!-- Pawn Gear -->
    <TKUtils.PawnGear.Temperature.Label>Show temperature information in the pawn gear command.</TKUtils.PawnGear.Temperature.Label>
    <TKUtils.PawnGear.Temperature.Tooltip>Include a pawn's temperature tolerance range in the pawn gear command (!mypawngear). Enabling this removes temperature information from !mypawnbody.</TKUtils.PawnGear.Temperature.Tooltip>
    <TKUtils.PawnGear.Apparel.Label>Show currently equipped apparel in the pawn gear command.</TKUtils.PawnGear.Apparel.Label>
    <TKUtils.PawnGear.Apparel.Tooltip>Include a pawn's current apparel in the pawn gear command (!mypawngear).</TKUtils.PawnGear.Apparel.Tooltip>
    <TKUtils.PawnGear.Armor.Label>Show armor values in the pawn gear command.</TKUtils.PawnGear.Armor.Label>
    <TKUtils.PawnGear.Armor.Tooltip>Include armor protection values in the pawn gear command (!mypawngear).</TKUtils.PawnGear.Armor.Tooltip>
    <TKUtils.PawnGear.Weapon.Label>Show currently equipped weapon in the pawn gear command.</TKUtils.PawnGear.Weapon.Label>
    <TKUtils.PawnGear.Weapon.Tooltip>Includes the weapon a pawn is currently equipped with in the pawn gear command (!mypawngear).</TKUtils.PawnGear.Weapon.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Pawn Health -->
    <TKUtils.PawnHealth.Surgeries.Label>Show queued surgeries in the pawn health command.</TKUtils.PawnHealth.Surgeries.Label>
    <TKUtils.PawnHealth.Surgeries.Tooltip>Includes currently queued surgeries in the pawn health command (!mypawnhealth).</TKUtils.PawnHealth.Surgeries.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Pawn Work -->
    <TKUtils.PawnWork.Sort.Label>Sort work priorities in the pawn work command.</TKUtils.PawnWork.Sort.Label>
    <TKUtils.PawnWork.Sort.Tooltip>If enabled, work priorities will be sorted like the Work tab in the pawn work command (!mypawnwork). This means work will be displayed as the Work tab from left to right.</TKUtils.PawnWork.Sort.Tooltip>
    <TKUtils.PawnWork.Filter.Label>Filter work priorities in the pawn work command.</TKUtils.PawnWork.Filter.Label>
    <TKUtils.PawnWork.Filter.Tooltip>If enabled, disabled work priorities will be removed from the pawn work command's output (!mypawnwork). This means work priorities a pawn is incapable of doing, or is not assigned to, will be omitted from the command's
        response.
    </TKUtils.PawnWork.Filter.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Abandon -->
    <TKUtils.Abandon.Method>How pawns should leave when the leave command is invoked.</TKUtils.Abandon.Method>
    <TKUtils.Abandon.Thanos>Thanos</TKUtils.Abandon.Thanos>
    <TKUtils.Abandon.MentalBreak>Mental break</TKUtils.Abandon.MentalBreak>
    <TKUtils.Abandon.Gear.Label>Colonists that leave by the leave command drop their inventory.</TKUtils.Abandon.Gear.Label>
    <TKUtils.Abandon.Gear.Tooltip>If a viewer chooses to leave the colony by the leave command (!leave), they'll empty their inventory (including an worn items) before departing.</TKUtils.Abandon.Gear.Tooltip>
    
    
    <!-- Tweak Group -->
    <TKUtils.CommandTweaks>Command Tweaks</TKUtils.CommandTweaks>
    
    <!-- Balance Coin Rate -->
    <TKUtils.CoinRate.Label>Show a viewer's calculated coin rate in the balance command.</TKUtils.CoinRate.Label>
    <TKUtils.CoinRate.Tooltip>If enabled, Utils will include the amount of coins a viewer earns per interval in the balance command's output (!bal).</TKUtils.CoinRate.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Balance in Buy Item -->
    <TKUtils.BuyItemBalance.Label>Show a viewer's remaining balance after buying an item.</TKUtils.BuyItemBalance.Label>
    <TKUtils.BuyItemBalance.Tooltip>If enabled, Utils will include the viewer's remaining balance after purchasing an item.</TKUtils.BuyItemBalance.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Command Parser -->
    <TKUtils.CommandParser.Label>Use Utils' flavor of command handling.</TKUtils.CommandParser.Label>
    <TKUtils.CommandParser.Tooltip>Older users would remember this as its command parser.</TKUtils.CommandParser.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Command Prefix -->
    <TKUtils.CommandPrefix.Label>Command prefix</TKUtils.CommandPrefix.Label>
    <TKUtils.CommandPrefix.Tooltip>The prefix to use for all Twitch Toolkit commands.\n\Prefixes cannot start with a:\n - /\n - .\n - contain spaces</TKUtils.CommandPrefix.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- General Group -->
    <TKUtils.General>General</TKUtils.General>
    
    <!-- Star -->
    <TKUtils.DecorateUtils.Label>Add a little star beside Utils in the mod list command.</TKUtils.DecorateUtils.Label>
    <TKUtils.DecorateUtils.Tooltip>because why not?</TKUtils.DecorateUtils.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Versioned Mod List -->
    <TKUtils.VersionedModList.Label>Include mod versions in the mod list command.</TKUtils.VersionedModList.Label>
    <TKUtils.VersionedModList.Tooltip>By default, the mod list command (!installedmods) only outputs mod names. This tweak allows you to include mod versions along side the names.</TKUtils.VersionedModList.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Emojis -->
    <TKUtils.Emojis.Label>Use emojis in some commands.</TKUtils.Emojis.Label>
    <TKUtils.Emojis.Tooltip>Allows Utils to use emoticons over text in some commands, like !mypawnhealth. If this is disabled, emoticons will be substituted with text.</TKUtils.Emojis.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Pawn Kind -->
    <TKUtils.PawnKind.Label>Allow viewers to specify their pawn's kind when buying.</TKUtils.PawnKind.Label>
    <TKUtils.PawnKind.Tooltip>If enabled, viewers will be able to specify their pawn's kind when buying a pawn (!buy pawn [race]).</TKUtils.PawnKind.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Lookup Limit -->
    <TKUtils.LookupLimit.Label>Maximum number of results in the lookup command.</TKUtils.LookupLimit.Label>
    <TKUtils.LookupLimit.Tooltip>The maximum number of results that will be displayed in the lookup command (!lookup). A higher value may create walls of text.</TKUtils.LookupLimit.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Hair Color -->
    <TKUtils.HairColor.Label>Dye viewer's hair color to match their chat color.</TKUtils.HairColor.Label>
    <TKUtils.HairColor.Tooltip>If enabled, users will have their hair dyed to match their current chat color.</TKUtils.HairColor.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Store Loading -->
    <TKUtils.StoreRate.Label>The number of items the store will process per tick.</TKUtils.StoreRate.Label>
    <TKUtils.StoreRate.Tooltip>With a previous update, Utils made Toolkit's store immediately visible. Utils runs a background task to ensure the store is up-to-date with the latest items in the game. This setting changes how many items it will process per
        tick until complete.
    </TKUtils.StoreRate.Tooltip>
    
    <!-- Dump Style -->
    <TKUtils.DumpStyle.Label>Json dump style</TKUtils.DumpStyle.Label>
    <TKUtils.DumpStyle.Tooltip>This setting changes how Utils dumps its shop data. If single file is selected, the default, the mod will write a single file containing its shop data. If multi-file is selected, Utils will write a single file for each
        category of data.
    </TKUtils.DumpStyle.Tooltip>
    <TKUtils.DumpStyle.SingleFile>Single file</TKUtils.DumpStyle.SingleFile>
    <TKUtils.DumpStyle.MultiFile>Multi-file</TKUtils.DumpStyle.MultiFile>
    
    
    <!-- Work Priorities Group -->
    <TKUtils.WorkPriorities>Work Priorities</TKUtils.WorkPriorities>
    
    
    <!-- Pawn Stats Group -->
    <TKUtils.PawnStats>Stats</TKUtils.PawnStats>
    
    
    <!-- Experimental Group -->
    <TKUtils.Experimental>Experimental</TKUtils.Experimental>
    
    <!-- Offload Shop -->
    <TKUtils.OffloadShop.Label>Offload saving shop data to a separate thread.</TKUtils.OffloadShop.Label>
    <TKUtils.OffloadShop.Tooltip>If enabled, the mod will save shop data on a separate thread.\n\nWarning: This could lead to unexpected behavior.</TKUtils.OffloadShop.Tooltip>
</LanguageData>
